piedmontng.com 2019-05-01

# Piedmont Natural Gas | Privacy Policy

_Last updated August 1, 2015_

Piedmont Natural Gas Company, Inc. (“Piedmont”) and is subsidiaries values the privacy of its customers.  Piedmont also believes that individuals should be empowered to protect their own information.  This Policy is intended to give users of this website (the “Site”) information on what information Piedmont collects on this site, how Piedmont uses that information, and choices that users have regarding their information.  Any questions or concerns by a user regarding the privacy of his or her information in connection with this Site should be directed to Piedmont through the means as specified in section 8 below.

You will receive e-mail communications from us when you sign up for an account online, perform an online transaction (such as paying your bill, requesting a new password, etc.) or opt in to receive marketing e-mails from us. If you have opted to receive marketing e-mails, we may contact you via e-mail about new products and services.  To opt out of receiving these marketing e-mails, please log into your online account and edit your profile. 

This Policy covers only information collected on or through this Site from individuals and businesses using Piedmont’s services. We only collect personal information if you voluntarily provide it such as through online account access. 

Piedmont may change the terms of this Policy at any time.  If we do so, we will notify you here.  The date at the top of this page will reflect the last update.  You should check this page regularly to check for updates. Your continued use of this Site after any changes in these terms constitute your agreement with these terms. Piedmont reserves the right to modify or discontinue this Site at any time.

_1\. Information Collected_  
Piedmont collects some personal information from users of this Site.  Examples of personal information that Piedmont collects from you include:

  * Contact information (including name, email address, physical mailing address, telephone number and similar information that you provide) 
  * User name and password; 
  * Date of birth; 
  * Social security number and driver’s license number; 
  * Bank account information if you choose the automatic draft option of payment; 
  * Information about your computer and browser; 
  * Customer service requests 

Piedmont uses “cookies” to remember user preferences and to maximize the performance of our website and services.  For example, cookies help Piedmont identify returning users so that you do not need to enter your account information every time you pay your bill. 

Piedmont also uses technology to count visitors to the Site and analyze how visitors use the Site.  This information generally is anonymized instead of being used to identify a particular user. 

Piedmont also maintains log files of traffic that visits the Site.  Piedmont’s services are designed to automatically record the information that you or your web browser sends when you visit the Site.  These log files include information such as your requests, IP address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your system.

_2.  No Assurances of Privacy_  
Piedmont will take commercially reasonable steps to safeguard all personal information provided by you using this Site from unauthorized access and use.  These measures are designed to protect such personal information from unauthorized person when you are using this Site.  Unfortunately data, including e-mail and electronic communications, submitted over the Internet is subject to the risk of being accessed by unauthorized third parties.  No security system is fail-safe and Piedmont cannot guarantee the information you provide will never be obtained by unauthorized persons.  By using this website, you acknowledge and accept this risk.

There are some steps you can take to help protect your own personal information.  For example, if you utilize our customer service options, including viewing your bill, a password or PIN number may be required. Maintaining the confidentiality of this password is your responsibility, and you should change your password if you suspect confidentiality has been compromised. The following steps may help safeguard information: (a) do not share your ID or password with anyone; (b) change your password regularly; (c) remember to sign off once you have submitted an application for a service online, or completed a secure online session; and (d) only provide your access ID when your browser indicates an encrypted connection, such as Secure Socket Layer (SSL), directly to the Site or to another site you have investigated and fully trust.

As between you and Piedmont, any information or material submitted to Piedmont in connection with this Site is provided on a non-confidential and non-proprietary basis.  By submitting information and material through this Site, you authorize Piedmont to use that information.

_3.  Use of Information  
_Piedmont uses the information submitted through this Site for various purposes.   Account information submitted by Piedmont customers through online about access is used to provide the services requested by the customer and perform accounting, auditing, billing credit checking and collection activities.  If a legal dispute arises, Piedmont also may use the information in connection with that dispute.  Other information or material submitted by users of this Site may be used by Piedmont for any purpose on an unrestricted basis, including but not limited to reproduction, display, performance, modification, transmission and distribution. Piedmont is also free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how or techniques submitted to Piedmont for any purpose on an unrestricted basis.  Without limiting the foregoing, Piedmont uses the information that it collects to provide services to consumers; conduct research and analysis (for example, market and consumer research); analyze security; establish and manage Piedmont accounts; collect and process payments and complete transactions; provide customer support; analyze user behavior to customize users’ preferences; customize and improve the Site’s properties; analyze and develop new products, services and websites; perform accounting, auditing, billing and collection activities; investigate and protect against potential or actual criminal activity; comply with and enforce applicable legal requirements, agreements and policies; and perform other activities consistent with this Policy. 

_4.  Disclosure to Others  
_Piedmont does not intentionally reveal any personal information that is provided by you through this Site to any third parties, except (i) when requested to do so by providers of services that are provided under rules of confidentiality and under contract between Piedmont and a third-party vendor and are necessary for the provision of such services; or (ii) when requested by a governmental agency having jurisdiction, or by a court of competent jurisdiction or other operation of law; (iii) when Piedmont believes disclosure is necessary and appropriate to prevent physical, financial or other harm, injury or loss or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity or exposure to legal liability, or (iv) other legitimate business purpose such as credit checking, collection or customer service activities. 

_5\. Managing Information You Provide  
_You can stop providing the information collected by Piedmont through this Site simply by ceasing to use the Site.  You also can choose to no longer provide personal information through this Site by ceasing to provide it.  Piedmont will retain some of the information you already provided such as cookies and anonymized data. For example, if you are a customer and you choose not to provide information through this Site, we will continue to store your account information.  Please note that if you choose not to provide the information requested by this Site regarding your account as a customer, Piedmont may not be able to provide you services. 

If you believe that any personal information you submitted through this Site to Piedmont is no longer accurate, please provide updated information by contacting Piedmont through the means specified in section 8 below. Please note that Piedmont does not permit changes that violate the law or any legal requirement. 

_6.  No Assurances Regarding Other Websites_  
Any non-Piedmont web site accessed through this Site is independent from Piedmont.  Piedmont has no control over such independent sites and is not responsible for the availability, content or use of those sites, including any link contained in those sites or any changes or updates to those sites. Piedmont makes no representations whatsoever about any other site you may access through this Site. Reference by Piedmont to another site does not mean Piedmont endorses or accepts responsibility for the content or use of that independent site or has any association with it or its operators.

_7.  Applicable Law and Forum_  
You agree that these terms and conditions and your use of this Site are governed by the laws of the State of North Carolina. You hereby consent to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts in Charlotte, North Carolina for any claim or dispute arising from these terms and conditions or the use of this Site. You are responsible for compliance with all applicable laws.

_8.  Contacting Piedmont  
_If you have any questions or concerns pertaining to the privacy or security of your personal information, you can contact us by:

  * Email  
  * Phone  
1-800-752-7504 
  * Mail  
Piedmont Natural Gas  
P.O. Box 33068  
Charlotte, NC 28233 

Other questions or concerns may be addressed by visiting our [Contact Us](http://www.piedmontng.com/about/aboutpng/contactus/contactus.aspx) page.

|
